usf.edu 2011-01-08

# Privacy Policy - University of South Florida

University of South Florida  
4202 E. Fowler Avenue  
Tampa, FL 33620 

To search for USF departments, visit the [A-Z Index.](http://mercury.fastmail.usf.edu/About-USF/azindex/index.asp)

To search for USF faculty and staff, visit the [Directory.](http://directory.acomp.usf.edu/?logo=1)

To search the USF Web site, use the [Search.](http://www.usf.edu/About-USF/search.asp)

To view a map and complete contact information for all USF System institutions and campuses, including USF, USF St. Petersburg, USF Sarasota-Manatee and USF Polytechnic, visit the [USF System Area Map.](http://system.usf.edu/system-overview/system-area-map.asp)

Thank you for visiting the University of South Florida home page. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy for official USF websites is to collect no personal information about you when you visit an official USF website unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit official USF websites, our Web servers automatically recognize only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed that website, and keep track of the types of operating systems, screen resolutions, and other hardware related items that help us make our site more accessible. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, we may gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our websites by collecting information on the date, time and website pages accessed by visitors to the website. We do this so that we can improve the content of our website and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and individual visitor's personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share information with us - by sending us a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information - we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law or by your specific permission.

Please be aware that as a large university with more than 47,000 students, faculty and staff, there are many websites within the usf.edu domain. This policy relates to those websites on which USF conducts its official business. Because we encourage the development and deployment of technology in an environment of academic freedom, we cannot ensure that all websites within the usf.edu domain are in strict compliance with this policy at all times.

If you have other questions about our privacy policy, or have ideas about improving our policies, please feel free to e-mail [webmaster@admin.usf.edu](mailto:) or phone us at (813) 974-4014.
